A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1 FA772
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges from China, 4
  - Tibet Study Group - Background and Planning, 1991 December 4-15 (Box 77, Folder 1186)
  - Tibet Study Group - Cities and States Visited, 1991 December 4-15 (Box 77, Folder 1187)
    San Francisco, New Mexico, Washington, DC, and New York City. Materials relating to hotels and travel added to this file.
  - Tibet Study Group - Itinerary, Namelists, Guidelines, 1991 December 4-15 (Box 77, Folder 1188)
  - Tibet Study Group - Meeting with Dalai Lama's Brother, 1991 December 4-15 (Box 77, Folder 1189)
    A small group of American and Tibetan nonprofit leaders (including NCUSCR president David Lampton) met at Tibet House on November 26, 1991. It is not known what relation this meeting has to the Tibet Study Group.
  - Tibet Study Group - Reports, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1991 December 4-15 (Box 77, Folder 1190)
    File includes itinerary and namelist. Reports concern the American delegation's visit to China and Tibet, July 28 - August 7, 1991.
  - Human Rights Research Delegation - Background and Planning, 1991 December 4-18 (Box 77, Folder 1191)
    Delegation conposed of Hu Gang and Yang Jiemian, from the Chinese Institute for Peace and Development Studies.
  - Human Rights Research Delegation - Cities Visited, 1991 December 4-18 (Box 77, Folder 1192)
  - Human Rights Research Delegation - Guidelines, Report, and Itinerary, 1991 December 4-18 (Box 77, Folder 1193)
  - Liaoning Provincial Environmental Protection Bureau Delegation - General, 1992 March 28-April 12 (Box 77, Folder 1194)
    Includes Background and Planning, Itinerary, Guidelines, Follow-Up
  - Liaoning Provincial Environmental Protection Bureau Delegation - Cities Visited, 1992 March 28-April 12 (Box 77, Folder 1195)
    New York, Washington, DC, Chicago, Los Angeles, Sacramento, San Francisco.
  - Information Economics Delegation - Background, Planning, Itinerary, Namelist, Brochure, 1992 April 25-May 16 (Box 77, Folder 1196)
  - Information Economics Delegation - Cities Visited (Honolulu), 1992 April 25-May 16 (Box 77, Folder 1197)
    File includes paper by Meheroo Jussawalla and Yale Braunstein, "Information Theory and Telecommunications: A Non-Specialist's Primer."
  - Information Economics Delegation - Cities Visited, 1992 April 25-May 16 (Box 78, Folder 1198)
    San Francisco, Boulder, CO, Washington, DC, New York City.
  - Information Economics Delegation - Reports, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1992 April 25-May 16 (Box 78, Folder 1199)
  - Mayors Delegation - Background, Planning, Itinerary, Namelists, Guidelines, and Brochure, 1992 May 30-June 14 (Box 78, Folder 1200)
    Materials concerning proposed Democratic Convention Observation Group added to this file.
  - Mayors Delegation - Cities Visited, 1992 May 30-June 14 (Box 78, Folder 1201)
  - Mayors Delegation - Correspondence, 1992 May 30-June 14 (Box 78, Folder 1202)
  - Mayors Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1992 May 30-June 14 (Box 78, Folder 1203)
  - Mayors Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1992 May 30-June 14; FA772:039; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 1203)
    Group photo of delegation at Disneyland; follow-up snapshots sent by Diane Schlagel.
  - U.S. History and Culture Study Delegation - Background, Planning, Namelists, Guidelines, and Brochure, 1992 May 30-June 18 (Box 78, Folder 1204)
  - U.S. History and Culture Study Delegation - Cities Visited, 1992 May 30-June 18 (Box 78, Folder 1205)
    New York, Providence, Boston, Washington, DC, Lincoln, NE, and San Francisco.
  - U.S. History and Culture Study Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1992 May 30-June 18 (Box 78, Folder 1206)
  - Intergovernmental Fiscal Relations Delegation - Background, Planning, and Budget, 1992 July 3-24 (Box 78, Folder 1207)
  - Intergovernmental Fiscal Relations Delegation - Cities Visited, 1992 July 3-24 (Box 78, Folder 1208)
    Toronto, Ottawa, Albany, New York, Washington, DC, Lansing, Ann Arbor, and San Francisco.
  - Intergovernmental Fiscal Relations Delegation - Guidelines and Articles, 1992 July 3-24 (Box 79, Folder 1209)
  - Intergovernmental Fiscal Relations Delegation - Report, Namelist, Itinerary, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1992 July 3-24 (Box 79, Folder 1210)
  - Multicultural and Minority Education Delegation - Background, Planning, Guidelines, Itinerary, Namelist, and Bios, 1992 September 9-27 (Box 79, Folder 1211)
  - Multicultural and Minority Education Delegation - Cities Visited, 1992 September 9-27 (Box 79, Folder 1212)
    New York, Washington, DC, Raleigh-Durham, NC, Santa Fe and Albuquerque, NM, Los Angeles.
  - Multicultural and Minority Education Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1992 September 9-27 (Box 79, Folder 1213)
  - Chen Liangjin Study Tour on Social Issues and Senior Citizens, 1992 October 15-20 (Box 79, Folder 1214)
    New York visits, arranged for Chen, a visiting scholar at Berkeley.
  - Grassroots Democracy and Economic Development Delegation - Articles, 1992 October 17-November 3 (Box 79, Folder 1215)
  - Grassroots Democracy and Economic Development Delegation - Background and Planning, 1992 October 17-November 3 (Box 79, Folder 1216)
  - Grassroots Democracy and Economic Development Delegation - Cities Visited, 1992 October 17-November 3 (Box 79, Folder 1217)
    New York, Washington, DC, Richmond, VA, Central Ohio, San Francisco.
  - Grassroots Democracy and Economic Development Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Brochure, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1992 October 17-November 3 (Box 79, Folder 1218)
  - Lu Ping Visit - Background (Arthur Andersen), 1992 November 5-12 (Box 79, Folder 1219)
    Lu Ping was director, Hong Kong and Macao Affairs Office, of the State Council of the PRC. His visit was cosponsored by Arthur Andersen and Co.
  - Lu Ping Visit - Expenses, 1992 November 5-12 (Box 79, Folder 1220)
  - Lu Ping Visit - Itinerary, Address, and Follow-Up, 1992 November 5-12 (Box 79, Folder 1221)
  - State Planning Commission Delegation - Background, Planning, Guidelines, and Articles, 1992 November 7-22 (Box 80, Folder 1222)
    Gui Shiyong, director of the SPC's Economic Research Center, led the delegation.
  - State Planning Commission Delegation - Cities Visited, 1992 November 7-22 (Box 80, Folder 1223)
    New York, Boston, Washington, DC, Houston, and San Francisco. Gui Shiyong, director of the SPC's Economic Research Center, led the delegation.
  - State Planning Commission Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelist, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1992 November 7-22 (Box 80, Folder 1224)
  - Zhang Wenpu Visit, 1992 November 11-26 (Box 80, Folder 1225)
    Ambassador Zhang Wenpu and Ms. Sun Aqing.
  - Hu Gang Visit, 1992 November 16-27 (Box 80, Folder 1226)
    Hu was president of the China Institute for Peace and Development Studies. His trip was originally proposed for October 1992.
  - China Institute for International Studies, 1992 December (Box 80, Folder 1227)
  - Urban Growth Management Delegation - Bios, Articles, and Planning, 1993 January 6-19 (Box 80, Folder 1228)
  - Urban Growth Management Delegation - Cities Visited, 1993 January 6-19 (Box 80, Folder 1229)
    New York, Washington, DC, Orlando, Phoenix, San Jos?, and San Francisco.
  - Urban Growth Management Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Brochure, Namelist, and Thank Yous, 1993 January 6-19 (Box 80, Folder 1230)
  - Liaoning Senior Judges Delegation, 1993 January 14-16 (Box 80, Folder 1231)
  - Hu Gang Visit, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 1232)
    Hu was president of the Chinese Institute for Peace and Development Studies. File consists solely of Tentative Itinerary, March 1-12. According to note on folder, additional files not found. A second Tentative Itinerary for a Chinese Institute of Peace and Deveopment Studies Delegation visit to New York, 1973 November 15-21, has been added to this file in processing.
  - Futures Trading Study Delegation - Correspondence and Planning, 1993 March 24-April 3 (Box 80, Folder 1233)
    Includes correspondence with Gao Shangquan and the State Commission for Restructuring the Economic Systems (SCRES), plus materials concerning visits to New York, Washington, and Chicago.
  - Futures Trading Study Delegation - Gao Shangquan (Postponed Trip), 1993 March 24-April 3 (Box 80, Folder 1234)
    Correspondence concerning a trip planned for October 1992.
  - Futures Trading Study Delegation - Lectures, 1993 March 24-April 3 (Box 81, Folder 1235)
  - Futures Trading Study Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Brochure, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1993 March 24-April 3 (Box 81, Folder 1236)
    Also includes Guidelines.
  - U. S. History and Culture Study Delegation - Background and Planning, 1993 May 7-25 (Box 81, Folder 1237)
  - U. S. History and Culture Study Delegation - Cities Visited, 1993 May 7-25 (Box 81, Folder 1238)
    New York, Washington, DC, Savannah, New Orleans, Tucson, and San Francisco.
  - U. S. History and Culture Study Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Brochure, Namelist, and Thank Yous, 1993 May 7-25 (Box 81, Folder 1239)
  - Shao Ning Visit, 1993 September (Box 81, Folder 1240)
    Shao Ning, from the Center for Economic Research of the State Planning Commission, was researching public financing and investment in infrastructure.
  - Ministry of Light Industry Delegation (Pan Beilei), 1993 June 6-15 (Box 81, Folder 1241)
    Vice Minister Pan Beilei led the delegation. The NCUSCR planned the New York leg of the visit, in conjunction with the Coca Cola Company.
  - Hubei Urban Planning and Development Delegation - General, 1993 July 9-21 (Box 81, Folder 1242)
    Includes Background and Planning, Report, Itinerary, Namelist, Brochure, and Guidelines.
  - Hubei Urban Planning and Development Delegation - Cities Visited, 1993 July 9-21 (Box 81, Folder 1243)
    New York, New Brunswick, Baltimore, Washington, DC, and St. Petersburg.
  - State Economic and Trade Commission (SETC) Delegation - Background and Planning, 1993 August 20-September 4 (Box 81, Folder 1244)
    Delegation focus was free enterprise.
  - State Economic and Trade Commission (SETC) Delegation - Cities Visited, 1993 August 20-September 4 (Box 81, Folder 1245)
    New York and Washington, DC. Delegation focus was free enterprise.
  - State Economic and Trade Commission (SETC) Delegation - Cities Visited, 1993 August 20-September 4 (Box 82, Folder 1246)
    Chicago, St. Paul, San Francisco. Delegation focus was free enterprise.
  - State Economic and Trade Commission (SETC) Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelists, and Brochure, 1993 August 20-September 4 (Box 82, Folder 1247)
  - Trade Policy Delegation (CCPIT) - Background, Reports, Itinerary, and Namelist, 1993 September 22-October 7 (Box 82, Folder 1248)
    China Council for the Promotion of International Trade.
  - Trade Policy Delegation (CCPIT) - Cities Visited, 1993 September 22-October 7 (Box 82, Folder 1248)
    New York, Washington, DC, Kansas (Kansas City), Seattle, and San Francisco.
  - Trade Policy Delegation (CCPIT) - Fax Correspondence, 1993 September 22-October 7 (Box 82, Folder 1250)
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs (CPIFA)Delegation - Background and Planning, 1993 October 15-30 (Box 82, Folder 1251)
    Ambassador Liu Shuqing led the delegation.
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs (CPIFA)Delegation - Itinerary, Namelist, Brochure, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1993 October 15-30 (Box 82, Folder 1252)
    Ambassador Liu Shuqing, president, led the delegation. There is no report in the file.
  - Primary and Secondary School Principals Delegation - Background and Planning, 1993 October 27-November 13 (Box 82, Folder 1253)
  - Primary and Secondary School Principals Delegation - Guidelines, Namelist, Itinerary, Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1993 October 27-November 13 (Box 82, Folder 1254)
  - Mikhail Titarenko Visit, 1993 October 28-November 2 (Box 83, Folder 1255)
  - Sustainable Development Delegation (SPC) - Background, Planning, Namelist, Itinerary, and Brochure, 1993 November 5-17 (Box 83, Folder 1256)
    Delegation from the State Planning Commission, also described as Environmental Leaders Delegation.
  - Sustainable Development Delegation (SPC) - Visits and Meetings, 1993 November 5-17 (Box 83, Folder 1257)
    New York, Washington, DC, Maryland, Pennsylvania, and Honolulu. Delegation from the State Planning Commission, also described as Environmental Leaders Delegation.
  - Sustainable Development Delegation (SPC) - Follow Up and TQ-Report, 1993 November 5-17 (Box 83, Folder 1258)
  - Economic Journalists Delegation - Fax Correspondence, 1994 January 21-February 5 (Box 83, Folder 1259)
  - Economic Journalists Delegation - Visits, Meetings, and Travel Arrangements, 1994 January 21-February 5 (Box 83, Folder 1260)
    Original folder labeled "Briefings." Materials concerning Travel added to this file.
  - Economic Journalists Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelist, and Brochure, 1994 January 21-February 5 (Box 83, Folder 1261)
  - Zhang Wenpu Visit, circa 1994 February 2 (Box 83, Folder 1262)
    Zhang was vice president of the Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs. The National Committee appears to have met with him during his visit and held a dinner for him.
  - China Center for International Studies (CCIS) Delegation - Background and Planning, 1994 February 16-26 (Box 83, Folder 1263)
    Ambassador Li Luye, director-general of CCIS, headed up the delegation.
  - China Center for International Studies (CCIS) Delegation - Correspondence with China Center for International Studies, 1994 February 16-26 (Box 83, Folder 1264)
  - China Center for International Studies (CCIS) Delegation - Ford Foundation Proposal and Correspondence, 1994 February 16-26 (Box 83, Folder 1265)
  - China Center for International Studies (CCIS) Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Brochure, Bios, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1994 February 16-26 (Box 83, Folder 1266)
  - Higher Education Administrators and Researchers Delegation - Background and Planning, 1994 March 20-April 12 (Box 83, Folder 1267)
    The NCUSCR worked in conjunction with Texas A & M University and arranged meetings and logistics for the delegation in New York and Washington, DC.
  - Higher Education Administrators and Researchers Delegation - Briefing Book, 1994 March 20-April 12 (Box 84, Folder 1268)
    Includes Itinerary, Namelist, and Briefing Materials (in English and Chinese).The NCUSCR worked in conjunction with Texas A & M University and arranged meetings and logistics for the delegation in New York and Washington, DC.
  - Higher Education Administrators and Researchers Delegation - Visits and Meetings (New York and Washington, DC), 1994 March 20-April 12 (Box 84, Folder 1269)
  - University Leaders Delegation - Background and Planning, 1994 April 13-26 (Box 84, Folder 1270)
  - University Leaders Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1994 April 13-26 (Box 84, Folder 1271)
    New York, Washington, DC, Columbus, OH, and Los Angeles.
  - University Leaders Delegation - Report, Intinerary, Namelists, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1994 April 13-26 (Box 84, Folder 1272)
  - University Leaders Delegation - Report, Intinerary, Namelists, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1994 April 13-26; FA772:040; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 1272)
    5 unidentified snapshots of delegation.
  - Shanghai Urban Development Delegation (SIIS) - Briefings, Bios, and Planning, 1994 April 20-May 3 (Box 84, Folder 1273)
    Delegation from the Shanghai Institute for International Studies. Includes tentative itinerary. The file does not includes any report on the delegation.
  - Shanghai Urban Development Delegation (SIIS) - Correspondence w- China, 1994 April 20-May 3 (Box 84, Folder 1274)
    Delegation from the Shanghai Institute for International Studies.
  - Primary and Secondary Education Delegation - General, 1994 May 11-28 (Box 84, Folder 1275)
    Background and Planning, Namelists, Guidelines, and Brochure.
  - Primary and Secondary Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1994 May 11-28 (Box 84, Folder 1276)
    New York, Boston, Washington, Ann Arbor, and San Francisco.
  - Primary and Secondary Education Delegation - Report and Follow-Up, 1994 May 11-28 (Box 84, Folder 1277)
  - Primary and Secondary Education Delegation - Report and Follow-Up, 1994 May 11-28; FA772:041; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 1277)
    7 snapshots of delegation
  - Minority Education Delegation - Fax Correspondence with State Education Commission, 1994 September 16-October 1 (Box 84, Folder 1278)
  - Minority Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1994 September 16-October 1 (Box 84, Folder 1279)
    Washington, DC, Oklahoma City, San Antonio, and Los Angeles. Material concerning travel planning added to this file.
  - Minority Education Delegation - Report, Namelists, Guidelines, Itineraries, and Brochure, 1994 September 16-October 1 (Box 84, Folder 1280)
  - Minority Education Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1994 September 16-October 1 (Box 85, Folder 1281)
  - Minority Education Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1994 September 16-October 1; FA772:042; Still Image (Box 146, Folder 1281)
    3 snapshots of Sheree Willis, Debra Kam, Han Yongjiu, at Oklahoma City University.
  - Hong Kong Legislative Council Delegation - Background and Planning, 1994 September 20-30 (Box 85, Folder 1282)
  - Hong Kong Legislative Council Delegation - Appointments in Washington, DC, 1994 September 20-30 (Box 85, Folder 1283)
  - Hong Kong Legislative Council Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelist, Brochure, and Bios, 1994 September 20-30 (Box 85, Folder 1284)
    Original folder labeled "USIA Report."
  - Hong Kong Legislative Council Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1994 September 20-30 (Box 85, Folder 1285)
  - Rural Development Delegation - Background and Planning, 1994 October 10-15 (Box 85, Folder 1286)
    Material concerning Washington, DC, meeting a visit planning added to this file.
  - Rural Development Delegation - Namelists and Bios, 1994 October 10-15 (Box 85, Folder 1287)
  - Publishers Delegation - Background and Planning, 1994 October 19-November 1 (Box 85, Folder 1288)
  - Publishers Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1994 October 19-November 1 (Box 85, Folder 1289)
    New York, Washington, DC, Nashville, and San Francisco.
  - Publishers Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelists, Brochure, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1994 October 19-November 1 (Box 85, Folder 1290)
  - China National Investment and Guaranty Corporation Delegation - Background, Planning, Namelist, Itinerary, and Brochure, 1994 December 3-12 (Box 85, Folder 1291)
  - China National Investment and Guaranty Corporation Delegation - Fax Correspondence with Chinese, 1994 December 3-12 (Box 86, Folder 1292)
  - China National Investment and Guaranty Corporation Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1994 December 3-12 (Box 86, Folder 1293)
    New York, Washington, DC, Los Angeles, and San Francisco.
  - China National Investment and Guaranty Corporation Delegation - Thank You and Follow Up, 1994 December 3-12 (Box 86, Folder 1294)
  - Chinese Women's Media Delegation (Canceled), 1995 March 12-29 (Box 86, Folder 1295)
    Proposal for NGO forum meetings, followed by program at University of Iowa.
  - Ministry of Finance Delegation (Canceled), 1995 March 23-28 (Box 86, Folder 1296)
    The delegation was to have been sponsored by the Asian Development Bank.
  - Mergers and Acquisitions Delegation (Canceled), 1995 Spring (Box 86, Folder 1297)
    Proposal for delegation from the State Council Research Office to study privatization, mergers, and bankruptcy. Includes correspondence with Ford Foundation representatives.
  - Shanghai Municipal Judges Delegation - Background, 1995 April 1-15 (Box 86, Folder 1298)
    File contains several papers on Constitutionalism and the role of judges in China.
  - Shanghai Municipal Judges Delegation - Correspondence, Namelist, and Itinerary, 1995 April 1-15 (Box 86, Folder 1299)
    Includes correspondence relating to the hiring of an interpreter.
  - Shanghai Municipal Judges Delegation - Meetings, 1995 April 1-15 (Box 86, Folder 1300)
    Includes some press coverage.
  - Shanghai Municipal Judges Delegation - Report and Thank Yous, 1995 April 1-15 (Box 86, Folder 1301)
    USIA Report. File includes brochure.
  - Foundation Leaders Delegation - Background and Planning, 1995 April 21-May 5 (Box 86, Folder 1302)
  - Foundation Leaders Delegation - Background and Planning, 1995 April 21-May 5 (Box 86, Folder 1303)
  - Foundation Leaders Delegation - Background on Chinese NGOs, 1995 April 21-May 5 (Box 86, Folder 1304)
  - Foundation Leaders Delegation - Brochure, Namelists, Bios, 1995 April 21-May 5 (Box 86, Folder 1305)
  - Foundation Leaders Delegation - Cities Visited, 1995 April 21-May 5 (Box 86, Folder 1306)
    Includes booklet and materials on NGO Conference (Workshop on the Nonprofit and Foundation Sector), April 24-26, at White Oak Plantation, Yulee, FL.
  - Foundation Leaders Delegation - Funding, 1995 April 21-May 5 (Box 87, Folder 1307)
    Includes materials on expenses to be billed to the Gilman Foundation.
  - Foundation Leaders Delegation - Report and Itinerary, 1995 April 21-May 5 (Box 87, Folder 1308)
    Report to the Ford Foundation.
  - Foundation Leaders Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1995 April 21-May 5 (Box 87, Folder 1309)
  - Engineering Education Delegation - Background, Planning, Guidelines, Namelist, and Brochure, 1995 May 6-21 (Box 87, Folder 1310)
  - Engineering Education Delegation - Fax Correspondence with State Education Commission, 1995 May 6-21 (Box 87, Folder 1311)
  - Engineering Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1995 May 6-21 (Box 87, Folder 1312)
    Washington, DC, Boston, Kansas City, Topeka, and Los Angeles.
  - Engineering Education Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1995 May 6-21 (Box 87, Folder 1313)
  - Mayor of Shanghai Xu Kuangdi Visit (Canceled), 1995 July 24 (Box 87, Folder 1314)
  - University Presidents Delegation, 1995 October 1-3 (Box 87, Folder 1315)
    Visit arranged in cooperation with Nelson Young, of the Hsu Chung Ching Educational Foundation of Hong Kong.
  - Institute of World Development Delegation, 1995 October 4-9 (Box 87, Folder 1316)
  - High Technology Research and Development Delegation - Background, Planning, Guidelines, and Brochure, 1995 October 11-27 (Box 87, Folder 1317)
    The visit focused on high technology research parks and software development.
  - High Technology Research and Development Delegation - Fax Correspondence with State Education Commission, 1995 October 11-27 (Box 87, Folder 1318)
  - High Technology Research and Development Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1995 October 11-27 (Box 87, Folder 1319)
    Washington, DC, Philadelphia, Salt Lake City and Orem, UT, San Francisco and Silicon Valley.
  - High Technology Research and Development Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1995 October 11-27 (Box 87, Folder 1320)
  - Shaanxi Judges Delegation, 1995 November 10-13 (Box 88, Folder 1321)
  - Legislative Modernization Delegation - Background, Planning, Namelist, and Itinerary, 1995 December 1-16 (Box 88, Folder 1322)
  - Legislative Modernization Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1995 December 1-16 (Box 88, Folder 1323)
    New York, Washington, DC, Madison, Denver, Sacramento, and San Francisco.
  - Legislative Modernization Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1995 December 1-16 (Box 88, Folder 1324)
  - Infrastructure Financing and Economic Restructuring Delegation (SPC) - Background, Planning, and Brochure, 1996 May 31-June 12 (Box 88, Folder 1325)
    Delegation from the State Planning Commission, led by Chen Tonghai.